In the next notebook, you're going to learn a technique that will let you integrate
在下面的笔记本中 你需要学习一种方法
any function of a single variable and all it's going to take is a loop.
利用一个单变量的函数 它的功能就是代入一个循环
Before you jump into this code,
在查看代码前
let me briefly explain the theory behind what you're going to be doing.
我先介绍一下相关原理
So, let's say you want to integrate velocity with respect to
假设你想计算和时间相关的速度
time but your velocity is given by some pretty complicated function,
但速度是一个非常复杂的函数给出的
as is often the case in the real world.
这在真实世界中往往如此
And let's say you want to use this velocity data to
假设你要使用这个速度数据
calculate your displacement from T equals one to T equals five.
计算从 t=1 到 t=5 之间的位移
How do you calculate the area when the shape isn't a rectangle?
当形状不是矩形时 如何计算面积？
The trick is this, you just don't.
我们的方法是 不用计算面积
Instead, you approximate.
只要算近似就可以了
So, let's start by making a really bad approximation,
因此 我们刚开始会有一个很差的近似值
where we just pretend the speed at the beginning is
我们假设开始速度就是整个
the speed throughout the entire four-second time interval.
4 秒间隔的速度
Well then, our area,
这时候 我们的面积
it's just the height times the width.
就是高度乘以宽度
And in this case, the height would be the value of
在本例中 高度等于
the velocity function evaluated T equals one, and the width.
速度函数在 t=1 时候的估算值 然后是宽度
Well, that's just the time interval Delta T,
它刚好时间间隔 Δt
which in this case is four seconds,
这里是 4 秒
but clearly, this is a really bad approximation.
但很显然 这是个很差的近似
It fails to account for all of this area above the line.
它没考虑到线上的所有面积
But no problem, let's improve our approximation.
不过没问题 我们改进一下这个近似
One way to do that is by breaking the single interval with a Delta T of
一种办法是 把单个时间间隔 Δt 分割为
four seconds into four time intervals with Delta T of one second.
四个小的时间间隔 每个间隔 1秒
And then, for this first time interval, from T equals one to two,
这时候 对于第一个时间间隔 从 t=1 到 2
we just draw a rectangle,
我们可以画一个矩形
and then we use the velocity T equals one as the velocity for the whole interval.
然后使用这个速度 t=1 作为整个间隔的速度
And then, we just repeat this procedure for two to three, three to four,
然后 我们对于后面的 2 到 3、3 到 4 区间重复这个步骤
and for T equals four to five and this
直到 t= 4 到 5
will give a better approximation of the actual area under the curve.
这样 我们就得到了曲线下面积的更好的估算
But you probably notice it isn't perfect.
但你可能注意到 这也不完美
In addition to underestimating in the first two segments,
前两个区间少估算了
it actually overestimates in this last segment.
而且后一个区间多估算了
So, while this is an improvement,
因此 这样有进步
it's still just not good enough.
但还是不够好
Had we solved the problem? Well, we chop our graph up into smaller rectangles.
我们怎么解决这个问题？我们把图分割成更小的矩形
For example, we could use a time interval of half-a-second,
例如 我们使用 0.5 秒作为区间
and this is definitely getting better,
这样就好多了
but we could go even smaller.
但区间还可以更小
As we reduce the width of these time intervals closer and closer to zero,
随着我们缩短时间间隔 使其趋近 0
we're going to get closer and closer to the true area under the curve.
我们就能越来越接近曲线下的真正面积
Okay, sorry. That's enough talking from me.
好的 抱歉 我就讲到这里了
I get very excited about the class.
很高兴能和你一起探讨
Why don't you go ahead and do this yourself?
下面 是你自己的动手时间